# **BRUNO CODINHA**

# **IT STUDENT**

@ bruno.codinha@tecnico.ulisboa.pt

**\** +351910477440

**♀** Lisbon, Portugal

github.com/SkyVandal

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Software Engineer

#### **AGILE-TM**

August 2022 - present

Servicenow

• Developer in a scrum team, in a company specialized in ServiceNow.

# Software Engineer

#### **INESC-INOV**

## July 2021 - September 2021

Django

• Developer in a scrum team, in the main research center for Computer Science and Engineering in Portugal.

# Software Engineer

#### Veertly

Mary 2020 - January 2021

React

Git Javascript

 Developer in a mid-sized team on a virtual event platform for a startup.

# Research Intern

# **INESC-INOV**

## July 2020 - September 2020

 Developer in a scrum team, in the main research center for Computer Science and Engineering in Portugal.

#### Mentor

#### **NAPE-IST**

July 2020 - Present

 Supported students in their academic journey and developed tools to aid their studies.

# Collaborator

### **IEEE**

May 2019 - Present

 Developer on an international organization in a multitude of initiatives to aid student's performance.

### **ABOUT ME**

My goal is to envision and conceive tools that can aid solving human's largest challenges.

I see myself both as a practical engineer and a devoted craftsman. I have been in touch both with Software and Science since an early age, coding on my own and researching endless documentaries and articles.

I come from a very multicultural background and have a wide range of interests, from blues music and football to competitive chess and classic literature.

# **LANGUAGES**

| Portuguese |  |      |       |       |   |   |  |   |   |  |  |
|------------|--|------|-------|-------|---|---|--|---|---|--|--|
| English    |  | <br> | <br>_ | <br>- |   | _ |  |   | _ |  |  |
| French     |  |      |       |       | - |   |  |   |   |  |  |
| Spanish    |  |      |       | <br>  |   | _ |  | _ |   |  |  |

#### **EDUCATION**

M.Sc. in Computer Science and Engineering **Instituto Superior Técnico** 

Sept 2020 - ongoing

B.Sc. in Computer Science and Engineering Instituto Superior Técnico

Espt 2017 - ongoing

International Highschool

**European School of Brussels II** 

# **PROJECTS**

| Brisa   |                       |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |
|---|-----------------------|--|--|--|--|--|--|--|
| 🛗 September 2022 - present  | ServiceNow JavaScript |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |
| <ul> <li>Working as a software engineer on a project for Brisa, which is the<br/>largest private road operator in Portugal. The project consists in<br/>automating their vulnerability response processes.</li> </ul> |                       |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |
| YARIS   |                       |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |
|   | Docker                |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |
| <ul> <li>Worked as a software developer of<br/>operations in the Gulf of Guinea.</li> <li>3500 professionals.</li> </ul>  |                       |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |
| Cryptocurrency Tool   |                       |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |
| Abril 2020 - Present  | Python Java Linux     |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |
| Developer of automation tools to<br>administrator of dedicated servers  |                       |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |
| CS IEEE Repository  |                       |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |
| May 2019 - Present  | C/C++ HTML            |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |

• Maintainer of a widely used codebase for supporting University's students on projects.